(Amy:)You don't hear me bitching about it.
(Amy:)A word of advice.
Moody seIf-obsession is only attractive...
(Amy:)...in men who can play guitar
and are considerably taller than you.
(Leonard:)I'm not moody, I'm fun.
Do you have any evidence
to support that statement?
(Leonard:)Well, hey,
I'm just as much fun as you are.
(Penny:)Really?
Are you willing to draw a mustache...
(Amy:)...on your finger
as a conversational icebreaker?
(Amy:)I am.
(Leonard:)Okay, fine. What do you suggest?
(Amy:)We just had a lovely meal.
(Amy:)The band is on fire.
(Amy:)And you're sitting next to a beautiful
woman wearing whorish makeup.
Why don't we head out on the floor...
(Amy:)...and see if I can sweat
through these dress shields?
(Leonard:)Once again,
I'm really not much of a dancer.
(Amy:)Don't worry, I'll lead.